So,
yeah, John Doe has received Is this a
new color? John Doe has received
quite some balance changes. Holy cow,
that's massive. What?
Yo.
>> [gasps]
>> Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait.
Okay, there's no way it's going to cover
that actually.
Uh okay, there's someone there. Um I
don't know if it opens up for this map
at all, but anyway,
wow, I'm just really surprised that
footprint I mean, I don't know what
that's going to do,
but it's
pretty big. It's pretty big, bro.
Yo, what is this building been doing?
Okay, I see a noob over there.
So, just uh go after them.
Oh, they are full boxed. Wow.
Also, we're like way bigger. I think
they finally added that thing where like
Hold on, I'm going to attract those. Um
I think they finally added that thing
they meant to add a while back.
Pretty annoying.
Did I time it right? I don't think I
timed it right. Yeah, I know I didn't.
All right, they're going down there.
All right, that looks like a plan.
>> [groaning]
>> But yeah, they made John Doe like way
bigger than before. It's actually pretty
insane how massive he is now. Hello.
I don't want to say that J in last. I
guess I'll go after the basic car. Why
is the generator highlighted?
Oh, cuz it got completed. Wait.
What the
Oh, there's like new objectives now?
I didn't even know that part of the
update. Okay. Uh this guy's going down
this corner, so just going to try and do
some stuff with this.
Stuff like that stuff to loop. Oh,
they're going down. Okay.
How does it get here? What Why is
everyone in that corner? Oh my gosh.
Uh if the Jane tries to stun, I'll
parry. Okay, they're not trying to.
All right, there we go.
Speed for 6 seconds.
Oh hold on, she is kind of far.
My I'm one range. Okay, there we go.
All right. Uh we're saving the Jane
last, so let's go after Deuce Car. Yes.
All right, took that out.
They go back to their team though.
They're unfortunate.
I'll punch
for me.
I do have to get this Deuce Car out.
Ooh, that was the big jukes.
Okay, did I parry? I parried.
Nice.
All right, one hit.
I'm going to spike here.
All right, there we go.
Should be chopped off?
Yeah, it is.
Very nice.
Barely got that hit.
I
Oh shoot, I didn't even know I had
resonance. I thought they were just
hatching the hatchet.
It's ain't going too well.
Thank you. Uh-huh, damn it.
Okay, might have to try to spike here.
Okay, nice.
Pretty good stuff. Who is
Hello.
I did not mean to press 404. I kind of
just wasted that.
L misclick.
All right, I'll be able to do something
with this.
Ooh, I like knocked them out of the way,
then they didn't snipe me.
Oh, they're cornering themselves.
Oh my gosh, that uh that like plus four
spikes actually just saved me there. But
I kind of just uh missed my M1 so um
not exactly the greatest.
Going guest.
All right.
Oh shoot, I wasn't paying attention.
That's my bad.
I should be praying Jane Doe like way
more. I don't know why I'm not.
No way. Oh wait, no, they're trapped.
Okay.
What? Oh my gosh, I didn't curve it
enough.
Yo, I'm about to lose.
Wait, where did he even go? Oh, there he
is.
Uh we got to watch out for their gun
and the Jane.
I need to be like way more aware of the
Jane. Dude, I'm missing every M1 too.
I'm like actually so ass.
Okay.
Let's go after uh guest. They did just
use some of their cash trying to save
the chance so we can try to capitalize
off that.
I think I probably could have had better
footprint spots too. I don't think these
footprints are even that good overall.
Going to spike that.
Ooh, you are full boxed. Wait, can I
just block this? Oh no, I can't. I'm not
that big.
If they block, I'm just going to use 404
so it's whatever.
I'm not going to try to block bait. Oh,
never mind. I have to use it for this.
I do have my spikes back so I could just
parry with that.
Or they just unblock.
There we go.
We have got the custom LMS guy but we're
kind of like
in an area like this so you know.
I think we should be able to chop this
off.
Yeah, all right. Oh shoot, this area.
Maybe I should have put foot there.
I don't know.
We got to be careful of their hot
Okay, that's one hit.
All right, we destroyed their shadow
point. That's really good.
All right, nice. We trapped them.
Shadow make use of this speed a little
bit. Careful stamina.
Probably Oh, wait. We don't have
resonance. We don't even have to care
about a hot
All right, nice. GG's.
What the
Wait, where's my outro?
Uh
Oh, there's like a little
a little just like brief intermission.
Okay, that's that's kind of cool, I
guess.
Um yeah, I really like the um
I didn't find that many uses for the
like retract
um quality of life, but the 31 spikes
I I could definitely like feel that. The
spikes definitely felt just like a
little bit longer. There's definitely
like
more opportunities for like those longer
spikes, which is really nice.
And also
um what's it called? Just the bigger
footprint. It kind of depends on the map
cuz
Yeah, I I don't I don't know. I also got
to learn like new footprint spots for
maps cuz, you know, then the maps all
got changed. I never really
figure that out. But
Yeah.
Yeah, like the size buff
to John Doe's actually like Oh, I I
don't think they added it to yourself.
That's interesting.
Uh Ooh, let's see. Does it Yeah, this is
not about a cover.
Wait, let let's see the hit box. Oh,
hell no.
>> [laughter]
>> Yeah, never mind. I was getting kind of
greedy with that. Uh Ooh, it can cover
this though.
That's pretty nice. Uh I'm probably
going to have to be like at that other
one, but yeah. Let's uh get one here.
Um just like that and uh
Oh, what the
I'm going to dive for that, buddy.
Oh, you're a slowed, buddy.
Wait, I didn't Oh, the Does the hit box
take a second to appear?
The heck?
>> [screaming]
>> I thought that was just a visual thing.
Does the hit box like actually take like
a good second to appear now because of
how it's bigger? That's interesting.
Okay.
Um
Hello.
Did I get him?
I can't tell.
No, I didn't. I got this person though.
Yes, all right. Let's try this.
Wait.
That was kind of dumb, low-key.
Nice damage.
What the Why is it all the way in the
corner here?
Okay, well, now you're cornered.
If only I would hit my M1s.
There we go.
Um yeah, so my footprints are low-key
really bad right now. Let's
um
try to fix those up. We got one here.
Oh, hello.
Were you a building man? Oh, and now
you're a dead man.
Nah. Not tough?
All right.
Let's get one here.
Once again.
Uh we have the good old one there. That
one is the ass one. We got to get that
replaced.
See that.
We just completed another generator.
And then we have to get this one
replaced.
Okay.
The two time is healing at a dispenser,
I can see. I probably want to kill this
building man.
Where is the two time?
That would also be really great.
Oh, here's the dispenser.
Let's try to get a little trap there.
That was horrible. Wait, where
I am so dumb.
All right.
Let's bring those down.
So they don't use it to loop.
And let's get this guest out of here.
Hold up.
All right, where did they go? Oh,
they're there.
Ooh, we got some death. Oh my gosh, did
I just full box them?
Oh wait, I forgot I can retract it.
Wait.
So they're trapped and then I
Yo, wait the retract is pretty nice for
that.
That's no longer a full iframe too, so
we still get some damage.
We don't have to worry about hitting the
block because we can just parry.
Oh, that knockback is kind of crazy
though.
And maybe that wasn't worth it.
Yeah, that lucky wasn't worth it. I
should have just block baited a bit
more.
Um how much cool down we have? About
that. Okay.
Yeah, we got to like reset the chase
somehow. Not sure where to do it though.
Um
You can get to make something happen.
Now once they start going back here
you can start making some plays with
that.
They should be trapped, right? I can
hear their footsteps though. Oh yeah,
there they are.
How nice.
Uh we need a third footprint. Let's get
it like here.
Just why not?
Okay.
Let's go find this building, man.
I can hear their sentry. It's like
I don't know.
Somewhere up there, I believe.
I hear like some building. Maybe it's
just their uh dispenser.
I don't know though.
Okay, so they just trapped themselves.
That's really nice.
Oh, there's their uh
Wait.
Okay, they're trapped.
No.
Oh wait, are they still trapped? Please.
Yes. Oh my gosh.
Just barely.
Holy.
And then there's just a little cutscene
at the end, I guess.
Geez.
This is a new killer spawn.
I didn't even think I was going to be
killer. I
Like there was someone with more malice.
I guess they must have been AFK or
something. Um anyway.
Not sure what this will do.
Just going to test stuff out. See if the
spray over there might want to
get that up. Anyway,
um
Preferably I like one back there. I
don't know why I didn't set that up
actually. What am I even doing?
It's a chance gambling though, so I will
try to capitalize off that. That is
hella annoying. I will get the guest
out. Never mind. Oh, you're dead.
Lock because he's in danger.
All right.
I can use this to
I I don't hit them.
What?
Okay.
W B tracked.
I'm just going to keep chasing them.
Dude, my M lines are not on point today,
bro. I swear people are like juking more
than usual.
Anyway.
Get out of here.
They're not paying attention.
Let's get a footprint on them.
Okay, it is instant.
Crap.
It's a lot of momentum lost.
They used a ghost breaker for some
reason though, so I guess
Ooh, wait. Actually, you might be able
to block off both of those exits with
that footprint now. Wait.
Thank you.
Are there two chances or there are two
chances? Okay.
Hey, I want to test this. Um
So, like if you put it here
Ah, yo. That's pretty nice. That is
pretty nice.
Okay, that's a new footprint spot right
there. Um wait, if you put one here,
will it like block these two?
Maybe. Maybe, I don't know.
Uh and we'll also get
like Let me get this entry out first.
And then um
maybe we can like cover both of these.
This was a little greedy.
Dude, what is with these chances, bro?
I'm going to kill this person.
Okay, we finally got all the footprints
set up though, so that's very nice.
>> For safety.
>> Some good damage.
Just going to keep walking.
Uh
if that area is blocked off
then this could be a good spike.
Crap
Oh, the unstoppable lasted until after
that. Okay.
Oh my god. What are my M1s today?
I'm just like not hitting my M1s.
I'm going to get these chances out of
here, bro. They're being really
annoying.
Uh yeah, where's that? Oh, what are they
building?
Oh, that's a lot of damage.
Let's subtract this. I kind of just want
to
be able to reach them easier.
They might try to shoot me.
I'm just going to spike here.
All right, you're dead.
Now we got to find that V.
I'm going to try to like
predict some of their spots before they
um use them.
What?
Oh, I hit the builder on accident. I
didn't want to do that.
Yeah, let's see. Can I find any of the
V's spray spots? I don't know.
Um
I'm going to build that.
All right.
Let's see. Where are these Veronica's
spray spots?
I think I'm just going to chase them and
find out. Okay.
Probably.
Yeah, there's probably one over here.
There's one. Why did they go back into
me?
Might make it easier to chase them.
>> I'm Veronica. I see
>> Yeah, let's just try and see where their
spots are.
John Doe isn't the best killer in TV, so
there's that.
Actually, I was like not looking at my
stamina at all.
Just going to try to snipe for some
momentum. Nothing.
Sprinting is done.
I need to stay close to him so I can get
the highlight. There we go.
Oh, they just stepped in the footprint.
They just got into the slowness bottle.
All right, nice.
There goes the B.
Preferably I would like to get another
footprint up right before LMS. Let's get
that. Covers these two hopefully.
Hopefully.
There's a century there.
All right.
Now I've got to get after him.
This like occasional highlight is really
nice.
Hopefully that chopped them off.
Oh, no, it didn't. I didn't even need to
use 44 there. That sucked.
Jeez, it took me a while to freaking
start chasing them. All right.
One hit. Oh, they stepped in the
slowness.
Two hits.
Three hits. One more.
I can use spikes here. It's kind of
greedy.
Oh, I can hear.
There's a gap? Oh, that sucks.
I like flicked way too hard. Yeah, that
was really risky. Almost cost me the
game, but
we got him.
Oh, what the heck? Wait, sometimes it'll
do like a cutscene after and sometimes
it won't. Is that a bug?
I don't know.
But, that's probably enough of testing
the buffed John Doe.
I started to see some of the potential
with the bigger footprints on the
the map we were just on like cutting off
two exits with one. that was pretty
nice.
The retracting spikes is just a nice
quality of life.
And they were just overall some really
good buffs, especially the unstoppable.
Unstoppable did get some really nice
buffs, too.
So,
yeah.
Peace out. Have a good day.